NLRB Case Files 5240
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
NLRB Case Files
1962
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
National Labor Relations Board (NLRB)
5240
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Case files of the United States National Labor Relations Board.
5621146
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, October 05, 2005
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 08, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4057: James A. Gross NLRB Files /4057 AV: James A. Gross NLRB Audiocassettes /4057 P: James A. Gross NLRB Photographs /4124: James A. Gross Papers, Additional NLRB Research Files /4166: James A. Gross Additional NLRB Research Files /4232: James A. Gross Collection of NLRB 60th Annual Conference Files 5240: NLRB Case Files 5318: NLRB Briefs, Petitions and other Legal Documents 5355: NLRB vs. International Union of Operating Engineers Local 450 Court Documents 5435 OH: NLRB Oral History Project Miscellaneous 5609: Philip Ross Collection of NLRB Documents 5843 OHM: NLRB Oral History Project II Master Tapes 5843 OHT: NLRB Oral History Project II Transcripts 5906: NLRB Additional Case Files relating to Health Care 6008: Lechmere vs. NLRB Company Legal Files 6122m: NLRB "Hebrew Free Burial Association, Case AO-279" Papers 6171: NLRB Decisions by Stipulation: Classified Index of National Labor Relations Board Decisions and Related Court Decisions (DS Reports) 6266: NLRB Documents Relating to UAW Alleged Unfair Labor Practices at Caterpillar, Inc.
United States. National Labor Relations Board.
5621146
- Roadway Express Inc. [folder 1 of 3], 1962 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Roadway Express Inc. [folder 2 of 3], 1962 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Roadway Express Inc. [folder 3 of 3], 1962 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- John M. Smyth company, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Scope and Contents
  Folder 1 of 1
- Takin Brothers Freight Line, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Compliance File Only (Folder 1 of 2)
- Takin Brothers Freight Line, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Folder 2 of 2
- Takin Brothers Freight Line (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Spector Freight System [folder 1 of 3], 1962 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Spector Freight System [folder 2 of 3], 1962 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Spector Freight System [folder 3 of 3], 1962 (Box 1, Folder 9)